Mss.Ms.Coll.104
American Philosophical Society
- Series II. Correspondence-Hare Family, 1724-1965
  - Horace to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1899 August 1; No. 1534
    Wants boots made at Steigerwalts.
  - Horace to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1899 August 4; No. 1535
    Just came into town and forgot two letters - will mail them later.
  - _________ ? to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1899 August 7; No. 1536
    About a horse or a dog?
  - T. Truxtun Hare to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1899 August 7; No. 1537
    Pleasant journey up here with a man I knew.
  - Horace to Mama, 1899 August 9; No. 1538
    About boy engaged for $12. per month. Butler not needed this winter. Need boots.
  - Mary Hutchinson to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1899 August 13; No. 1539
    Announcing engagement to John Osborne Summer.
  - Horace to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1899 August 18; No. 1540
    Wants to know more about Mr. Brown's illness and whether to congratulate Minnie on her engagement.
  - Nancy to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1899 August 20; No. 1541
    On way to Caen. Description of market day. Of friends abroad - Mariana and Katharine.
  - Horace to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1899 August 27; No. 1542
    Out in mountain far from ranch in cabin for shooting.
  - Newspaper clippings, 1899 August; No. 1543
    Articles on Dreyfus Court Martial.
  - Mariana to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1899 September 3; No. 1544
    Distressed over changes in Grandpa at home. Frank Shaw. Theatres, concerts and dressmaking. On Bella staying abroad for winter. Travels from Denmark through Holland.
  - Esther to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1899 September 3; No. 1545
    Will return with Grandpa if Wellings can't have me. All about family activities. Climbed Green Mountain and social events and friends.
  - Richard Lears to Miss E.B. Hare, 1899 September 4; No. 1546
    Letter of admiration of you and want to see you when in Philadelphia.
  - Horace to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1899 September 4; No. 1547
    Fishing and shooting. Boots came, will do but not heavy enough.
  - Molly to Miss Esther Hare, 1899 September 7; No. 1548
    You are welcome to come whenever you please.
  - Rydie to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1899 September 9; No. 1549
    Pleasant journey home from Bar Harbor. Dined at Aunt Emily's. If Mr. and Mrs. Hare go to Hot Springs, couldn't you have house party and invite Herbert Lyman and Frank.
  - Horace to Mother, 1899 September 18; No. 1550
    Riding and looking at traps. Found bear that had been that had been trapped and shot it. About blacksmith bill. Lost pony. Never had a chance with Minnie, but now she's engaged, doing best to break engagement. Wonders if he should stay all winter. Boots unsatisfactory.
  - Minnie to Horace, 1899 September 18; No. 1551
    Cruised up St. Lawrence. At home with Mae now.
  - Emily to Miss Hare, 1899 September 23; No. 1552
    Acknowledging your "dollar". Would love to meet you in Newport for a day. Will see what turns up.
  - Newspaper clipping, 1899 September 24; No. 1553
    Article - Wedding of Julia Dent Grant to Prince Michael Cantacuzene.
  - Molly to Miss Esther Hare, 1899 September 25; No. 1554
    About races and you're not going. Expect Mrs. Beale and Conny and going to New York with Conny. Other visitors and social events.
  - Horace to Hon. J.I. Clark Hare, 1899 September 26; No. 1555
    Experiences at camp - trailing trapped bear and working for neighbor ($.75 a day).
  - Horace to Mrs. Hare, 1899 September 28; No. 1556
    Working for neighboring rancher. Indian visitors, exciting chase of bear but did not get him. Received note from Grandpa instructing me to come home and read law - not sure I care to. Interested in cattle business and living in West (where all men are equal).
  - Molly to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1899 October 5; No. 1557
    Accepting invitation to visit you at Radnor.
  - Horace to Mother, 1899 October 14; No. 1558
    On way to Hodge's Ranch with Dick Vaux. Am tough and dirty (take hot bath every 2 months)
  - Horace to Mother, 1899 October 17; No. 1559
    Note on way to Hodge's Ranch.
  - Cass to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1899 October 17; No. 1560
    Molly returned from her good time at "Harford". Clergyman (Philip Salinger) at church in Bennington. Work at Bellevue Hospital, Girl's Friendly and Sunday School. Princeton. Book - "Uncle Scipio".
  - Horace to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1899 September 4; No. 1560a
    Description of horseback ride up into mountains to camp and daily routine. Visit to miner's camp - got lost returning.
  - Horace to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1899 October 24; No. 1561
    Have not heard from anyone and need money. Camping and shooting.
  - A. Goadby to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1899 November 1; No. 1562
    Sending photo of you. Studying harmony. Saw Naval Parade with Mrs. Welling. Hoping to see you next summer in Bar Harbor.
  - Maria M.C. to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1899 November 4; No. 1563
    Anxiety over Edmund. He attended football game - you must be proud of Truxton. Glad to hear Horace returned from western trip in splendid condition. Sophie and Cousin Lizzie to be in Philadelphia three days - sure Lizzie would be glad to see you.
  - Mary Helen Cadwalader to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1899 November 11; No. 1564
    Pleasant and satisfying here. Anxious to talk to you about Rome after being abroad.
  - Margaretta to Miss Esther Hare, 1899 November 25; No. 1565
    Opera in Philadelphia. Going South in January. Sargent's portrait of Thomas a great work of art. Social events. Thoron's visit - Edith's friendship.
  - J. Wallace Hallowell to Judge Hare, 1899 December 1; No. 1566
    Bill for purchase of fruits.
  - Oliver H. Leigh to Hon. J.I. Clark Hare, 1899 December 11; No. 1567
    Request for you to pen two or three hundred words to use either in or as introduction to book (History). Enclosure - Newspaper article: my letter to "Telegraph" - "An Old Englander on England's Invasion of the House of the Boers".
  - Charles Willing Hare to Hon. J.I. Clark Hare, 1899 December 15; No. 1568
    Had enclosure - list of mortgages belonging to you and Mrs. Hare. Explanation of these mortgages.
  - Emily to Miss Hare, 1899 December 24; No. 1569
  - Daisy to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1899 December 30; No. 1570
    Going to country "Cake-Walk". Went to a colored concert and amusing description of colored "Arden Prima Donna".
  - Newspaper clipping, 1900; No. 1571
    Article - "Scott's Scrapbook". T. Truxtun Hare made Walter Camp's All-American 4 years in succession.
  - Elsie to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1900 January 6; No. 1572
    Thank you for hat brush.
  - Bertha F. Beale to Esther, 1900 January 13; No. 1573
    Thank you for book of Lord Nelson's life.
  - Willing to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1900 January 15; No. 1574
    Plans for your coming to New York. Accepted invitation from Katharine to dine with her Aunt. Inquiries as to family. About work and his associates and boarding house.
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1900 February 3; No. 1575
    Horace's dinner. Enclosures - invitation to dine at Mr. C. Hartman Kuhn's which I refused for you and Mr. Robert Riddle's calling card.
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1900 February 7; No. 1576
    (Private) Willing came home for weekend. About Horace's new step in life which he so much dreads, going to work in Bank. Truxtun came home this morning. Enjoyed evening at Mrs. Warrens. Mr. Tyler talked of Horace's coming into bank. Mrs. Cassatt.
  - _______ to Miss Hare, 1900 February 10; No. 1577
    Invitation to "Juvenile Party" - Mr. and Mrs. A. Drexel Biddle. Invitation - to visit Margaret Clemens. Invitation - from Mr. and Mrs. Cassatt to meet Mr. and Mrs. Robert Cassatt.
  - Cass to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1900 February 11; No. 1578
    Thank you for purse. Family news (especially about Mama and Molly). Did Katy go to Germany or is it only gossip?
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1900 February 14; No. 1579
    Enclosing invitation to Fortnightly Club.
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1900 February 15; No. 1580
    Willing's news. About Watson's bill for Grandma and Truxtun's college fee. Going to opera and next week to Baltimore. Horace shows interest in bank. Enclosed letter from Gimbel's in reference to account.
  - Helena R. Beale to Miss Esther Hare, 1900 February 27; No. 1580a
    Aunt Emily going to give Emily a lunch - I can hardly wait. Still taking riding lessons and going to have sewing class.
  - Mary S. Hutchinson to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1900 February 16; No. 1581
    Clearing up misunderstanding about letter when you were to meet John. Going to Boston to see about abiding place for next winter.
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1900 February 16; No. 1582
    Mrs. Parish has just invited us to go abroad in March. Shall we? Social events and family news. So glad you are able to do so much for Grandma and Grandpa - while you are with them, try to get them to tell of their early lives. Visited Mrs. Harry Brown - a picture of grief.
  - Willing to Miss Hare, 1900 February 16; No. 1583
    (letter to Mother, sent to Esther) Referring to his business and influential friends. Sunday at Katharine's (Tivoli), friends, skating and ice boating. (Discusses Livingstons and guests). Plans for you and maybe Harry to come to New York.
  - Rydie to Miss Esther Binney Hare, 1900 February 16; No. 1584
    Apology for not seeing you before you left. Called on Mariana. Where is "that book"?
  - Mariana to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1900 February 17; No. 1585
    Skating on river. Lunched with Ridie and talked of everyone. Frances Arnold visited. Going to Orpheum with Miss Woodville, supper at Mrs. Thomas Surettes and opera class.
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1900 February 23; No. 1586
    Sent your two waists. Visit to Baltimore (Colonial Dames). Home news and social events. About painting house.
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1900 February 24; No. 1587
    Enclosing letter for Grandma. Sent your batting dress (be careful, it gives fever). Social events (boys' costumes for "children's party").
  - Rydie to Miss Esther Binney Hare, 1900 February 27; No. 1588
    Frank Sears and the most enjoyable Assembly Ball. Day out at Radnor. Frank going to Palm Beach.
  - Esther to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1900 February 28; No. 1589
    Making plans with Margaretta for going to Europe, and enjoying her company. Grandpa and Grandma. Think you better tell Stuart it is impossible for you to go abroad May 2.
  - Penn Furniture Company to J.I.C. Hare, 1900 March 1; No. 1590
    Payment of rent for 1023 Market St.
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1900 March 1; No. 1591
    In reference to balance in Girard Bank. Gas bill. About plans for going abroad (Truxtun could go with us). Horace has German Measles (will have to call off luncheon for Emily). Had successful dinner.
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1900 March 4; No. 1592
    Have not seen Stuart, but will try to and think May 2nd a good date. Really want to go and go to a cure. Horace in bed with measles.
  - Palm Beach Inn to J.I.C. Hare & family, 1900 February & March; No. 1593
    Bills for Palm Beach Inn.
  - Emily to Miss Hare, 1900 March 4; No. 1594
    Weather, Horace's measles, my dinner, Mr. and Mrs. Elkins' dinner on night of blizzard, Willing's visit home and Truxtun's poetry. (This letter for Grandma Hare).
  - Constance R. Beale to Miss Esther Binney Hare, 1900 March 7; No. 1595
    Social and family news.
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1900 March 8; No. 1596
    Received checks, and on plans for sailing abroad.
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1900 March 8; No. 1597
    Horace over measles and going back to work (splendid position). Willing was home and he is pleased with his work. Stuart Smith was here about our sailing with him. (Do you think we can go early in May?) Talk it over with Grandma and Grandpa. Enclosed letter from Stuart Farrar Smith with rooms he's engaged for passage awaiting approval.
  - Stuart Farrar Smith to Miss Esther Hare, 1900 March 8; No. 1598
    Note scolding because you are "putting off" going abroad.
  - Nancy to Miss Esther Hare, 1900 March 8; No. 1599
    Went to Tivoli and visited Mary Livingston first and then Katharine over Washington's birthday. Guests there. "Going out a good deal in a quiet way". Jimmy's new horse.
  - Truxtun to Miss Esther Binney Hare, 1900 March 10; No. 1600
    Biddle's party fun, but rough. Passage arranged for track team for June 20.
  - Molly to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1900 March 10; No. 1601
    Went to Washington. Cass' surprise for me - Ridie came for a five day visit. Saw lots of our Bar Harbor friends in Washington. Praise for your going South to care for your grandparents. Visitors (Nancy Allen and Helen Waterman) and our activities.
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1900 March 12; No. 1602
    Told Stuart to give up cabin and we'll try to go abroad at a later date. Is Margaretta going at all? Discussing plans.
  - Katharine to Miss Esther Hare, 1900 March 12; No. 1603
    Announcement of engagement to Mr. Lawrence Simpson.
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1900 March 13; No. 1604
    Grandma's attack. Will come if you want me. More plans for sailing. Katharine Livingston engagement to Lawrence Simpson.
  - Helena to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1900 March 15; No. 1605
    Chimney fire. Visited Aunt Amy at Lewistown. Family news.
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1900 March 16; No. 1606
    Reassuring to hear Grandma is better. Making arrangements for a car or compartment for Grandma to return home by the 31st. Luncheon and "howling storm". Mrs. Hopkins died leaving a week old baby. Katharine Livingston's engagement.
  - W.W. Montgomery to Hon. J.I. Clark Hare, 1900 March 16; No. 1607
    Financial business letter. (Also have six children in bed with measles.)
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1900 March 17; No. 1608
    Concern over getting car for Grandma. Brought Laddie into town, and first night he ate up several things in parlor, so now sleeps on floor in my room. Clara's husband died and children were put in a home.
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1900 March 17; No. 1609
    Grandma's precarious condition. Think I better come down. Ask Mr. MacVeagh about getting a private car. Willing saw Katharine and her family are furious over her engagement. Mrs. Hopkin's death.
  - Grandmama Beale to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1900 March 17; No. 1610
    Distressed at your Grandmother's set-back, but just heard better news of her. Sympathy for you in helping in this experience. News of friends, family and social activites.
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1900 March 18; No. 1611
    Suggestion that I engage a private car, come down in it and help bring Grandma home.
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1900 March 19; No. 1612
    Encouraged by news of Grandma. Consolation to you in this experience. Urging you get her a car to return home. On boys and weather. Laddie - perfect house pet (has not eaten anything since my patent leather slippers).
  - Constance to Miss Hare, 1900 March 20; No. 1613
    Sympathy for you all in this anxiety over Grandma. Grandma Beale has bad leg and can't walk. Enclose ribbon for you.
  - Polly Coxe to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1900 March 20; No. 1614
    Saw Willing in New York before we sailed. People met and sights in travels.
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1900 March 21; No. 1615
    Play that Horace is in tonight at the Cassatt's - "A Question of Honour".
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1900 March 21; No. 1616
    About special car for bringing Grandma home.
  - Horace to Hon. J.I. Clark Hare, 1900 March 22; No. 1617
    About Grandma's return trip home and his work. Willing has been brought back from Yonkers and goes to Patterson.
  - Truxtun to Miss Esther Binney Hare, 1900 March 23; No. 1618
    "French Play" at University of Pennsylvania. Trip to Broadwater, Virginia. Ask Grandma to send check (I need money). Willing going to Patterson to learn more about gas!
  - Molly to Miss E.B. Hare, 1900 March 23; No. 1619
    What you are missing - dirty streets and air full of germs. Katharine's engagement. Horace acted splendidly in "Honour Bound" at the Cassatt's. Social activites.
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1900 March 23; No. 1620
    Wishing you all were home - and awaiting word as to whether to engage car. Willing and his duty to "gas". Dinners and luncheons I gave. Miss Woodward engaged to Prince Ruspoli. MacVeagh's offer of "car" for Grandma's return.
  - Esther to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1900 March 24; No. 1621
    Grandma improving slowly but very weak. Coming back in car with MacVeaghs.
  - Nancy to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1900 March 24; No. 1622
    Katharine's engagement (such a surprise). Jimmy's second horse "a secret". Social activities.
  - Maria M. Coxe to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1900 March 26; No. 1623
    General travel news and inquiries. Going now to Rome.
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1900 March 25; No. 1624
    About bringing Grandma home in MacVeagh's car. Dinner for the Parrishes and lunch for Emily and guests.
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1900 March 27; No. 1625
    Either Truxtun or I will meet you in Savannah. Which would you rather have come?
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1900 March 28; No. 1626
    Decided to send Truxtun to meet you. Willing left this morning to live and work in Patterson. Emma, your maid, also left this morning. Truxtun's French play is tomorrow night. Will have doctor and ambulance on hand when you arrive.
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1900 March 29; No. 1627
    Your returning home and who should meet you in Savannah.
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1900 March 30; No. 1628
    So unhappy over telegram saying you are not leaving till the 9th. Want you to come home with MacVeaghs and I will go down in your place.
  - E. Lawrence to Mrs. Hare, 1900 March 31; No. 1629
    In reply to a sympathy letter on death of step-mother.
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1900 March 31; No. 1630
    Truxtun good in "French play". Received telegram telling me not to come down, but if you need me telegraph at once.
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1900 April 2; No. 1631
    Going to meet MacVeaghs and will see about car. List of Grandmama's bequests. (Palm Beach, March 9, 1900) A private letter to Horace asking advice. (Grandma's condition - nothing Mama could do, but should I send for her? Grandma could take a turn for the worse anytime.)
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1900 April 3; No. 1632
    Went to meet MacVeaghs, but they won't arrive till tomorrow. Please send check (need money).
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1900 April 4; No. 1633
    Telegram - car will reach Palm Beach Monday. Mr. MacVeagh's arrangements for car.
  - Margaretta to Miss Esther Hare, 1900 April 5; No. 1634
    Your Mother and my Father making arrangements for car for you.
  - Esther and J.I.C. Hare to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1900 April 5; No. 1635
    Inquiries about private railroad car to take Grandma home.
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1900 April 6; No. 1636
    More about private car. Concert for soldiers and sailors - Admiral Dewey came to it and a dinner at the Cassatt's. You and Molly Coles to be K. Livingston's bridesmaids.
  - Robert M. Riddle to Miss Esther Hare, 1900 April 7; No. 1637
    Left two volumes of "Miss Bird's Japan" at your door - will you please see that they don't get lost?
  - _______ to Judge Hare, 1900 April 7; No. 1638
    Hotel bill. Two telegrams on private car. Pharmacy bill.
  - Esther and J.I.C.H. to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1900 April 9; No. 1639
    Troubles in making arrangements for car. Will you get in at Washington?
  - C.W.H. to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1900 April 27; No. 1640
    Got "down in dumps" because not making money and not looking forward to "year after year of slavery".
  - T.T. Hare to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1900 June 20; No. 1641
    On board. (S.S. Southwark) Willing saw me off.
  - C. Willing Hare to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1900 June 21; No. 1642
    On seeing Truxtun off. Enclosing lace collar for you.
  - Truxtun to Miss Esther Binney Hare, 1900 July 6, 8; No. 1643
    July 6 - Very pleasant trip so far. We perform at London Athletic Club and then go to Paris. July 8 - America won 8 out of 13 events yesterday - I got 2 medals.
  - M.C.M.V. to Miss Esther Hare, 1900 July 12; No. 1644
    Thank you for book. Pleasant voyage and mention of people on board.
  - N. to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1900 July 18; No. 1645
    I love it here, but Meta and Mother don't like it. Sure you and your Mother would not like it. Social activities. If we go to York, would like you to visit there.
  - Esther to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1900 July 19; No. 1646
    Plans for summer vacationing. Willing ordered to Connecticut. Grandpapa gave me money to pay for bridesmaid dress. General home news and social activities.
  - M.H.C. to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1900 July 27; No. 1647
    Description of place. Too small to urge you to visit.
  - Willing to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1900 August 5; No. 1648
    General family news letter.
  - Truxtun to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1900 August 6; No. 1649
    Sightseeing in Paris with Cousin E., John and Ned.
  - Willing to Mamma, 1900 August 7; No. 1650
    Experiences in New York with Harry and Fox and Arthur Cosby - dinner, a row over politics (Roosevelt), music hall, Hungarian restaurant and steam bath. Saw them off at dock.
  - M.E. Powel to Cousin Clarke, 1900 August 9; No. 1651
    Informing you of our Mother's death.
  - Maria M. Coxe to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1900 August 13; No. 1652
    Plans for your coming here.
  - Rydie to Miss Esther Binney Hare, 1900 August 20; No. 1653
    Lovely times here - men I've met and activities. Burned your letters - so don't worry.
  - Margaretta to Miss Esther Hare, 1900 August 22; No. 1654
    Leaving soon for home. May go to North Shore after getting home. Travels, sights and people, and slight description of Isle of Wight.
  - Ernest E. Parker to Miss E.B. Hare, 1900 September 21; No. 1655
    Enclose cap ribbon and photos. Had jolly times at Bar Harbor.
  - Willing to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1900 September 28; No. 1656
    Generator gave out and had to stop making gas - so town was in darkness. Temporary repairs have been made. Sprained my ankle.
  - Willing to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1900 October 1; No. 1657
    On crutches now. Have hired boy to help me dress. Ask Grandpa to deposit $75. for me so I can pay doctor. About your taking a trip to Milford.
  - Maria M. Coxe to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1900 October 4; No. 1658
    Family activities. Strike of coal miners (not miner's choice, but President Mitchell, United Mine Workers, intimidating men).
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1900 October 5; No. 1659
    Family news. Maid is trying to make an invalid of me.
  - Willing to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1900 October 5; No. 1660
    Still on crutches. Brundrett told me to come home, but want to stay to finish work. About your coming up.
  - Montgomery Nurseries to Mrs. Hare, 1900 October 26; No. 1661
    Bills for planting, stone, bulbs, etc.
  - John Cadwalader to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1900 November 13; No. 1662
    Business letter on Sioux City bonds. Have been following Truxtun in football games - has very fine qualities.
  - Mr. & Mrs. Walter Horstmann to Mr. T. Truxton Hare, 1900 November 23; No. 1663
    Invitation for December 11 from 5 until 7.
  - Margaretta to Miss Esther Hare, 1900 November 27; No. 1664
    Coming to Philadelphia, want you to lunch with me. Working for the first time in my life.
  - Willing to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1900 November 30; No. 1665
    Could not accept Cameron Forbes invitation for Thanksgiving dinner - business here. Visited school - saw Ollie (talked to his master and he's irresponsible, wild and hard to manage).
  - Mrs. Joseph Leidy, Jr., Miss Kathryn M. Leidy to Mr. Willing Hare, 1900 December 1; No. 1666
    Invitation - at home December 13 from 5 until 7. Thursdays in January after 4.
  - Willing to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1900 December 2; No. 1667
    Visiting Ollie at school, but he was in trouble again (always in trouble - has not got good sense). Mapping out where new gas lamps are to go. Truxtun's football.
  - Mrs. Alexander W. Biddle to Mrs. Horace Hare, 1900 December 5; No. 1668